{
  "words":[
    {
      "textQuestion": "It's an animal that can fly",
      "key1": "R",
      "key2": "I",
      "key3":"B",
      "key4":"D",
      "key5":"X",
      "textAnswer":"BIRD"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "It's the king of jungle",
      "key1": "L",
      "key2": "I",
      "key3":"O",
      "key4":"N",
      "key5":"K",
      "textAnswer":"LION"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "What is this grumpy yet surprised bird called?",
      "key1": "P",
      "key2": "O",
      "key3":"T",
      "key4":"X",
      "key5":"O",
      "key6":"O",
      "textAnswer":"POTOO"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A very, super, mega cute animal",
      "key1": "L",
      "key2": "A",
      "key3":"L",
      "key4":"A",
      "key5":"N",
      "key6":"M",
      "textAnswer":"LLAMA"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "Animal who likes to build their home by the river",
      "key1": "E",
      "key2": "B",
      "key3":"A",
      "key4":"E",
      "key5":"V",
      "key6":"T",
      "key7":"R",
      "textAnswer":"BEAVER"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "What is the most dangerous animal in Africa?",
      "key1": "I",
      "key2": "H",
      "key3":"P",
      "key4":"P",
      "key5":"I",
      "key6":"O",
      "textAnswer":"HIPPO"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "An informal restaurant, coffee shop that usually specializes in simple meals, coffees, and desserts.",
      "key1": "S",
      "key2": "A",
      "key3":"E",
      "key4":"F",
      "key5":"C",
      "textAnswer":"CAFE"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "An area of land, along with buildings and equipment, used to grow crops.",
      "key1": "A",
      "key2": "F",
      "key3":"R",
      "key4":"M",
      "key5":"T",
      "textAnswer":"FARM"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A place where goods are sold.",
      "key1": "R",
      "key2": "A",
      "key3":"M",
      "key4":"K",
      "key5":"E",
      "key6":"T",
      "key7":"O",
      "textAnswer":"MARKET"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A traveling show with clowns, acrobats, and other acts.",
      "key1": "R",
      "key2": "I",
      "key3":"C",
      "key4":"C",
      "key5":"U",
      "key6":"S",
      "key7":"G",
      "textAnswer":"CIRCUS"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A place with many rooms and beds where people pay money to sleep, eat meals, or buy other services.",
      "key1": "T",
      "key2": "O",
      "key3":"H",
      "key4":"E",
      "key5":"K",
      "key6":"L",
      "textAnswer":"HOTEL"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A place where things are sold",
      "key1": "O",
      "key2": "P",
      "key3":"S",
      "key4":"H",
      "key5":"I",
      "textAnswer":"SHOP"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A place where you go to take out money",
      "key1": "A",
      "key2": "B",
      "key3":"N",
      "key4":"I",
      "key5":"K",
      "textAnswer":"BANK"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A place where you go to watch a movie",
      "key1": "N",
      "key2": "E",
      "key3":"C",
      "key4":"I",
      "key5":"M",
      "key6":"P",
      "key7":"A",
      "textAnswer":"CINEMA"
    },

    {
      "textQuestion": "A food made by baking a dough of flour or meal",
      "key1": "B",
      "key2": "A",
      "key3":"E",
      "key4":"R",
      "key5":"K",
      "key6":"D",
      "textAnswer":"BREAD"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A long orange root vegetable",
      "key1": "R",
      "key2": "C",
      "key3":"R",
      "key4":"A",
      "key5":"O",
      "key6":"T",
      "key7":"E",
      "textAnswer":"CARROT"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A small, juicy fruit, with a smooth skin that is either green, red, or purple",
      "key1": "B",
      "key2": "G",
      "key3":"R",
      "key4":"A",
      "key5":"P",
      "key6":"E",
      "textAnswer":"GRAPE"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "The liquid from fruits is used for drinking.",
      "key1": "T",
      "key2": "E",
      "key3":"C",
      "key4":"I",
      "key5":"U",
      "key6":"J",
      "textAnswer":"JUICE"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "The seed of this grass, which is a very important food",
      "key1": "C",
      "key2": "R",
      "key3":"I",
      "key4":"E",
      "key5":"T",
      "textAnswer":"RICE"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A food made from flour, eggs, and water and dried in various forms, such as macaroni or spaghetti.",
      "key1": "T",
      "key2": "S",
      "key3":"A",
      "key4":"P",
      "key5":"A",
      "key6":"E",
      "textAnswer":"PASTA"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "To release air noisily from the lungs",
      "key1": "G",
      "key2": "O",
      "key3":"C",
      "key4":"U",
      "key5":"D",
      "key6":"H",
      "textAnswer":"COUGH"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "To cause pain, harm, or suffering to",
      "key1": "U",
      "key2": "R",
      "key3":"H",
      "key4":"T",
      "key5":"D",
      "textAnswer":"HURT"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A sport played on ice, with two teams of six skating players",
      "key1": "H",
      "key2": "C",
      "key3":"O",
      "key4":"K",
      "key5":"E",
      "key6":"Y",
      "key7":"A",
      "textAnswer":"HOCKEY"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A game whose players hitting a small ball back and forth over a net using racket",
      "key1": "N",
      "key2": "E",
      "key3":"T",
      "key4":"N",
      "key5":"I",
      "key6":"S",
      "key7":"Z",
      "textAnswer":"TENNIS"
    },
    {
      "textQuestion": "A game in which a club is used to hit a small ball into a hole in the ground",
      "key1": "F",
      "key2": "O",
      "key3":"G",
      "key4":"L",
      "key5":"U",
      "textAnswer":"GOLF"
    }
  ],
  "quiz":[
    {
      "question":"Hello, how can I help? - I want to book __________ a ticket.",
      "answer1": "advance",
      "answer2": "first",
      "answer3":"in advance",
      "answer4":"the first",
      "correct":"in advance"
    },
    {
      "question":"Jack couldn't pass the final _____________.",
      "answer1": "examinational",
      "answer2": "examine",
      "answer3":"examining",
      "answer4":"examination",
      "correct":"examination"
    },
    {
      "question":"If I were the Prime Minister, I _________ more money on education.",
      "answer1": "spent",
      "answer2": "will spend",
      "answer3":"would spend",
      "answer4":"spending",
      "correct":"would spend"
    },
    {
      "question":"If you want any further __________, you can contact to the head office.",
      "answer1": "questions",
      "answer2": "information",
      "answer3":"answers",
      "answer4":"responses",
      "correct":"information"
    },
    {
      "question":"Choose the word whose the position of primary stress differs from the three ones.",
      "answer1": "reputation",
      "answer2": "invitation",
      "answer3":"production",
      "answer4":"introduction",
      "correct":"production"
    },
    {
      "question":"He said that he ________ learning with you.",
      "answer1": "like",
      "answer2": "to like",
      "answer3":"liking",
      "answer4":"liked",
      "correct":"liked"
    },
    {
      "question":"Choose the word whose the underlined part is pronounced differently.",
      "answer1": "picture",
      "answer2": "lecture",
      "answer3":"furniture",
      "answer4":"cure",
      "correct":"cure"
    },
    {
      "question":"If there ________ gravity, water wouldn't run downhill.",
      "answer1": "aren't",
      "answer2": "isn't",
      "answer3":"wasn't",
      "answer4":"hadn't",
      "correct":"wasn't"
    },
    {
      "question":"When I saw Daisy, she said she was taking her driving test ____________.",
      "answer1": "today",
      "answer2": "the tomorrow",
      "answer3":"the next day",
      "answer4":"tomorrow",
      "correct":"the next day"
    },
    {
      "question":"_______ you want to keep fit, you should do more exercises",
      "answer1": "Although",
      "answer2": "However",
      "answer3":"If",
      "answer4":"Where",
      "correct":"If"
    },
    {
      "question":"These flowers ________ in a warm sunny place.",
      "answer1": "should be kept",
      "answer2": "keep",
      "answer3":"be kept",
      "answer4":"should be keep",
      "correct":"should be kept"
    },
    {
      "question":"A ________ is a piece of land that is a protected area for animals or plants",
      "answer1": "habitat",
      "answer2": "conservation",
      "answer3":"preserve",
      "answer4":"species",
      "correct":"habitat"
    },
    {
      "question":"He said that he ________ his homework since 7 o'clock.",
      "answer1": "had done",
      "answer2": "has done",
      "answer3":"was doing",
      "answer4":"did",
      "correct":"had done"
    },
    {
      "question":"I _________ my best suit because everyone else was very casually dressed.",
      "answer1": "needn't wear",
      "answer2": "needn't have worn",
      "answer3":"mustn't have worn",
      "answer4":"mustn't wear",
      "correct":"needn't have worn"
    },
    {
      "question":"Women only began to gain ________ with men in the 20th century.",
      "answer1": "fair",
      "answer2": "equality",
      "answer3":"same",
      "answer4":"balance",
      "correct":"equality"
    },
    {
      "question":"When I ________ here for fifteen years I'll be entitled to a pension.",
      "answer1": "am working",
      "answer2": "work",
      "answer3":"had worked",
      "answer4":"have worked",
      "correct":"have worked"
    },
    {
      "question":"This house was said _________ two hundred years ago.",
      "answer1": "to build",
      "answer2": "that have been built",
      "answer3":"that it built",
      "answer4":"to have been built",
      "correct":"to have been built"
    },
    {
      "question":"I donâ€™t believe a word he said. I think he just _________ that story.",
      "answer1": "made up",
      "answer2": "went away",
      "answer3":"turned up",
      "answer4":"got over",
      "correct":"made up"
    }
  ]
}